Nguyen Quoc Khanh

· Al Engineer Resume

Quarter 6, Linh Trung Ward, Thu Duc City, Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

□ (+84) 39-269-7777 | ■ nqkdeveloper@gmail.com | ♠ nqkhanh2002.github.io | 回 nqkhanh2002

"The secret of getting ahead is to get started."

Summary

Highly motivated and passionate in Artificial Intelligence. Experienced in writing codes and algorithms as well as building and deploying complex neural network through various programming language. Excited to use knowledge in machine learning/AI and statistical analysis to solve real-world problems and make the customer achieve more. Willing to develop values under company culture.

Education

Nguyen Du High School for the Gifted

Buon Me Thuot, Dak Lak

Mar. 2017 - Aug. 2019

SPECIALITY: PHYSICS

- GPA: 8.9/10
- Gold Medal in Physics Olympic 10-3 2017
- Gold Medal in Physics Olympic 10-3 2018

VNUHCM - University of Information Technology (UIT)

MAJOR: INFORMATION SYSTEM

- GPA: 8.8/10
- · Self-study master in Computer Science
- Interested in Computer Vision

Thu Duc, Ho Chi Minh

Aug. 2020 - Present

Work Experience

MAICO GROUP

Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

AI ENGINEER INTERN

May. 2022 - August. 2022

- Interned as an AI Engineer at MAICO Group, primarily focused on recommendation system development.
- Contributed to the development and enhancement of recommendation systems within the company's technological ecosystem.
- · Collaborated with the team to improve the accuracy and performance of the recommendation algorithms for enhanced user experience.

Vietnam Olympiad in Informatics (VNOI)

Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

July. 2020 - Dec. 2022

ALGORITHMIC PROBLEM SETTER

- Designed and tested algorithmic problems for competitive programming competitions.
- Conducted beta testing, considered time complexity, and provided sample input/output.
- · Collaborated with other designers, generated test data, and continuously improved the competition process.

CS-UIT Artificial Intelligence Club

Ho Chi Minh. Viet Nam

MACHINE LEARNING ENINGEER

Feb. 2020 - Present

- Organize training sessions on subject knowledge and skills used in AI competitions.
- Engage in self-study and participate in AI competitions to enhance expertise.

Skills

Data ScienceStrong math skills, ability to visualize and present data effectively, expertise in data mining techniques. Experienced in C/C++,

Java, and Python programming languages.

Deep LearningStrong foundation in mathematics for deep learning. Proficient in UI technologies such as Flask, Docker, and JavaScript. Experienced with deep learning frameworks such as TensorFlow, Keras, and PyTorch.)

Machine Learning Solid understanding of data structures, regression and classification algorithms, data modeling and predictive modeling

techniques. Proficient in popular ML tools such as scikit-learn and Keras.

Computer Vision Strong knowledge of image analysis algorithms, image processing and visualization techniques. Experienced with popular computer vision frameworks such as OpenCV, YOLO, TensorFlow, Keras, ONNX, TenssoRT, and Pytorch.)

Certificate

Mathematics for Machine Learning

Imperial College London

SPONSORED BY CALIFORNIA STATE LIBRARY

Mar. 2022

Apr. 2022

Machine Learning Specialization

Sponsored by California State Library

DeepLearning.Al

Mathematics for Machine Learning and Data Science Specialization

DeepLearning.Al

SPONSORED BY CALIFORNIA STATE LIBRARY

Apr. 2022

DeepLearning.AI TensorFlow Developer Professional Certificate

DeepLearning.Al Apr. 2022

SPONSORED BY CALIFORNIA STATE LIBRARY

Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) Specialization

DeepLearning.Al

Apr. 2022

SPONSORED BY CALIFORNIA STATE LIBRARY

Al for Medicine Specializationn
Sponsored by California State Library

DeepLearning.Al
Apr. 2022

TensorFlow 2 for Deep Learning Specialization

DeepLearning.Al

SPONSORED BY CALIFORNIA STATE LIBRARY

Apr. 2022

DeepLearning.AI TensorFlow Developer Professional Certificate

DeepLearning.Al Apr. 2022

SPONSORED BY CALIFORNIA STATE LIBRARY

DeepLearning.Al

TensorFlow: Data and Deployment Specialization
Sponsored by California State Library

Apr. 2022

Deep Learning Specialization

DeepLearning.Al

SPONSORED BY CALIFORNIA STATE LIBRARY

May. 2022

Natural Language Processing Specialization

DeepLearning.Al

SPONSORED BY CALIFORNIA STATE LIBRARY

June. 2022

TensorFlow: Advanced Techniques Specialization

DeepLearning.Al

SPONSORED BY CALIFORNIA STATE LIBRARY

July. 2022

Project

Advanced driver-assistance system by Computer Vision

Personal Project

VIEW SOURCE

May. 2023

• Overview: Development of a lane detection and tracking solution for self-driving cars. This is an important part of the autopilot system, to ensure the safety and efficiency of the driver and passengers on the road.

Vietnamese License Plate Recognition

Personal Project

VIEW SOURCE

July. 202.

• Overview: Recognizing Vietnamese license plates in the parking lot, which was utilized for both 1 and 2 rows of Vietnamese license plates. Using the KNN algorithm and the OpenCV image processing library.

Facial Expression Recognition

Personal Project

VIEW SOURCE

June. 2022

• Overview: Build and train a convolutional neural network (CNN) in Keras from scratch to recognize facial expressions and directly serve the trained model to a web interface and perform real-time facial expression recognition on video and image data.

Traffic Sign Classification Using Deep Learning in Python/Keras

Personal Project

VIEW SOURCE

Apr. 2022

Overview: Train deep learning models known as Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) to classify 43 traffic sign images. This project could be
practically applied to self-driving cars.

Detecting COVID-19 with Chest X-Ray using PyTorch

Personal Project

VIEW SOURCE

May. 2022

Overview: Use a ResNet-18 model and train it on a COVID-19 Radiography dataset. Our objective in this project is to create an image classification
model that can predict Chest X-Ray scans that belong to one of the three classes with a reasonably high accuracy.